(Sheldon:)Obesity.
(Bernadette:)I have the tool you wanted.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Raj:)You guys don't have
to go to the trouble.
I'm back in the money now;
(Raj:)I can just buy
another helicopter.
(Howard:)It's not about the money.
(Howard:)It's about solving a problem.
(Howard:)It's why I became an engineer.
(Howard:)It's what I like to do,
it's what I'm trained to do.
(Howard:)It's who I am.
(Sheldon:)Oh, look at you--
the little engineer that could.
(Bernadette:)Why don't you just
call tech support?
Hey!
Whoa!
Not cool!
(Penny:)What?
(Howard:)There's two kinds of
people in this world:
(Howard:)those who call
tech support
(Howard:)and those who make fun of the
people who call tech support.
(Bernadette:)I call tech support
all the time.
Ha-ha!
You call tech support!
What a baby!
(Headmaster:)And now, for our
commencement address,
(Headmaster:)one of our
most distinguished alumni,
(Headmaster:)noted Caltech physicist
Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
(Leonard(on screen):)Members of the faculty,
students,
(Leonard(on screen):)I'm excited to speak
to you today.